(Leonard:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)Do you want to say it?
(Amy:)Let's say
it together.
BOTH:
We're getting a turtle!
(Penny:)This is why I've been saying
we should keep champagne on ice.
(Sheldon:)Sarcasm?
(Amy:)Yes.
Okay.
(Sheldon:)That was tricky,
'cause when it comes to alcohol,
(Sheldon:)she generally means business.
Well, we're-we're
very happy for you.
(Amy:)Yes.
(Amy:)Thank you.
(Amy:)Acquiring a joint pet
is a big step for us.
(Sheldon:)No. It's true.
(Sheldon:)It means that we care so much
about each other,
(Sheldon:)there's enough left over
for an eight-ounce reptile.
(Leonard:)Why a turtle?
(Sheldon:)After much deliberation,
we've determined that a turtle
(Sheldon:)is the ideal pet.
(Sheldon:)They don't shed fur,
they don't make noise...
(Amy:)For Halloween, we can dress him
as a cobblestone.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Sheldon:)And if he ever goes berserk,
I know I can outrun him.
(Sheldon:)Coincidentally, that's also
why I chose you as a roommate.
(Leonard:)Well, congratulations.
(Leonard:)Who would've thought
you two would be the first
(Leonard:)in our group
to start a family?
Mm-hmm.
That's what I said!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪